Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Archelon: The Movie
Summer and the ocean!
And today is an important audition!
I'll pass and become a star!
And yet...
why are you guys here?!
Because we are the organizers of the audition!
What is this?!
It's the role of a turtle!
Huh? A turtle role?
Alright, without further ado...
Ready...
Action!
Umm...
I haven't even done anything yet!
Why are you just standing there?
Turtles are quadrupedal reptiles!
Moreover,
nowadays they are considered as close to dinosaurs as crocodiles are!
Dinosaurs
Pterosaurs (Extinct)
Crocodilians
Turtles
D-Dinosaurs...?
You can do it, Kanna-san!
Ready...
Action!
Quadrupedal reptile...
close to dinosaurs...
Looking good, Kanna-kun!
With this, you can even play "that" turtle role!
Eh?
What do you mean by "that" turtle role?!
That is Archelon!
Th-This turtle...
is huge!
Of course!
Archelon is said to be the largest ancient sea turtle in history!
Total length: 4 meters
Total width: 5 meters
Habitat: Cretaceous North America
A true big star in the sea turtle world!
So with that said,
ready... Action!
Since it's that big, it must be pretty heavy...
Whoa, what happened?!
Archelon's shell
was thoroughly lightweight;
its surface wasn't made of scales but a leathery skin,
and inside was just a framework of bones.
Its weight is said to be around 2 tons,
though there is also a theory that it was only about 400 kilograms!
Therefore, there's a possibility it could swim very fast!
Well, did you get it?
Hey,
What are you doing?
Can't you stand up?
I can't take this anymore! I quit!
Why?!
When I can't even stand on my own,
how could I ever become a big star like Archelon?!
Archelon has its weaknesses too!
As a result of reducing too many bones.
Archelon...
when laying eggs on land without buoyancy
for long periods...
Gravity
DANGER
Archelon's internal organs would be crushed
under its own weight!
DANGER
That's terrible then!
Not at all!
While other creatures began giving birth in the ocean,
changes in the marine environment during the Late Cretaceous
caused many of them to perish.
However,
that disaster didn't reach the sandy beaches.
The eggs of sea turtles like Archelon,
who kept laying eggs on land, remained safe!
And that was precisely because they never gave up on laying their eggs on land!
Without giving up...?
As a result,
sea turtles were able to overcome the barrier of 66 million years ago and survive!
and survive!
I...
won't give up after all!
I'm going to become bigger and bigger,
just like Archelon!
Alright! That's the spirit!
What???
She really became big!
Burst forth, my idol soul!
BIG BANG!
Indeed,
this world was made by the great turtles who never gave up!
It's a brand new world!
Big...
I will become....